animalpicturesarchive.com 2002-12-04

# Animal Pictures Archive's Privacy Policy

**Animal Pictures Archive's Privacy Policy**

[Animal Pictures Archive](http://www.animalpicturesarchive.com/) is committed to protecting the privacy of Internet users. Below is information outlining our continued support for the responsible management of user information.

[User Information] [As an Engage Affiliate]  

**  User Information**

* * *

Animal Pictures Archive does not collect any personally identifiable information about you such as name, address, phone number, or e-mail address. However, Animal Pictures Archive does obtain some types of non-personally identifiable information such as the Internet Service Provider you use to connect to the Internet, your browser type, or the type of computer operating system you use (Macintosh, Windows, or Linux for example). The information collected by Animal Pictures Archive is used for the purpose of analyzing the user survey only. This information includes: 

**Your IP address**
    a unique number assigned to every computer on the Internet. The type of information that Animal Pictures Archive can infer from the IP address is a geographic location. 
**Your domain**
    e.g., .com, .net, or .edu. This is standard information that is available with all communication sent on the Internet. 

Other information that Animal Pictures Archive can infer consists of: 

**Operating system** : e.g., Windows, DOS, Macintosh, or UNIX;
**Browser version and type** : e.g., Netscape Navigator or Internet Explorer;
**Browser language** : e.g., Java or Unix;
**Internet Service Provider (ISP)** : e.g., MindSpring or AOL

**  As an Engage Affiliate**

* * *

Animal Pictures Archive works with a third party that serves ads to this site. To find out more about how Engage manages the privacy of information in conjunction with serving ads on this site, please go to <http://www.engage.com/privacy>. 

If you have any additional questions about Animal Pictures Archive's privacy policy, please contact me at [jskim@AnimalPicturesArchive.com](mailto:jskim@AnimalPicturesArchive.com)
